[
    {
        "qid": 248393,
        "question": "Patient is a 24 year old male.<br>- The patient has felt confused or disorientated lately.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has been in contact with someone infected with the Ebola virus in the last month.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has noticed unusual bleeding or bruising related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has traveled to West Africa in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option2": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option3": "Ebola",
        "option4": "Pulmonary embolism",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "93%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 415813,
        "question": "Patient is a 17 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heartbreaking, haunting, like a knife stroke, and violent.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, left flank, upper chest, right hypochondrium, and epigastric region.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the thoracic spine and the right scapula.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient drinks alcohol excessively or has an addiction to alcohol.<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous and feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has vomited several times or has made several efforts to vomit.",
        "option1": "Chagas",
        "option2": "Boerhaave",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Anaphylaxis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 244867,
        "question": "Patient is a 9 year old male.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, thyroid cartilage, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 10 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has traveled to North America in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option2": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option3": "Croup",
        "option4": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "71%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 856081,
        "question": "Patient is a 5 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, thyroid cartilage, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has had a cold in the last 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has traveled to North America in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option2": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Epiglottitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 529822,
        "question": "Patient is a 63 year old male.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Panic attack",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "40%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 276243,
        "question": "Patient is a 7 year old male.<br>- The patient has felt confused or disorientated lately.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has had diarrhea or an increase in stool frequency.<br>- The patient has been in contact with someone infected with the Ebola virus in the last month.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous or feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has noticed unusual bleeding or bruising related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has traveled to West Africa in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "HIV (initial infection)",
        "option2": "Ebola",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Pneumonia",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "69%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 940538,
        "question": "Patient is a 55 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, and pharynx.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is immunosuppressed.",
        "option1": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option2": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option3": "Influenza",
        "option4": "Acute laryngitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "84%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 423620,
        "question": "Patient is a 5 year old female.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the left tonsil, thyroid cartilage, palate, and trachea.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has traveled to North America in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option2": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option3": "Epiglottitis",
        "option4": "Chagas",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 1022703,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old male.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has been more irritable or their mood has been very unstable recently.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Croup",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Acute otitis media",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "78%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 109146,
        "question": "Patient is a 9 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, palate, under the jaw, and trachea.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has had a cold in the last 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has traveled to North America in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Chagas",
        "option2": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option3": "Epiglottitis",
        "option4": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "82%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 130287,
        "question": "Patient is a 13 year old male.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient consumes energy drinks regularly.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has recently taken decongestants or other substances that may have stimulant effects.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option4": "Panic attack",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "74%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 29980,
        "question": "Patient is a 12 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heartbreaking.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, right flank, upper chest, belly, and epigastric region.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 10 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the thoracic spine and left scapula.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 9 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous or feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has vomited several times or has made several efforts to vomit.",
        "option1": "Boerhaave",
        "option2": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Pericarditis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "61%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 177632,
        "question": "Patient is a 59 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is haunting, sensitive, and sickening.<br>- The patient feels pain in the upper chest, hypochondrium (left), and epigastric regions.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the lower chest.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is significantly overweight compared to people of the same height.<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient has a burning sensation that starts in their stomach, goes up into their throat, and can be associated with a bitter taste in their mouth.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that get worse after eating.",
        "option1": "Unstable angina",
        "option2": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "option3": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option4": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "54%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 985534,
        "question": "Patient is a 57 year old male.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of the head, right cheek, left cheek, occiput, and right temple.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is exposed to secondhand cigarette smoke on a daily basis.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Cluster headache",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "72%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 317788,
        "question": "Patient is a 17 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heartbreaking, haunting, violent, and sickening.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, left flank, upper chest, belly, and epigastric region.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the right and left scapula.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 9 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient drinks alcohol excessively or has an addiction to alcohol.<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous or feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has vomited several times or has made several efforts to vomit.",
        "option1": "Boerhaave",
        "option2": "Chagas",
        "option3": "Pericarditis",
        "option4": "Anaphylaxis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]